[
  {
    "question": "venir",
    "answer": "kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "ser/estar",
    "answer": "sein"
  },
  {
    "question": "vivir/residir",
    "answer": "wohnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "tener",
    "answer": "haben"
  },
  {
    "question": "llamarse",
    "answer": "heißen"
  },
  {
    "question": "viajar",
    "answer": "reisen"
  },
  {
    "question": "correr",
    "answer": "laufen"
  },
  {
    "question": "jugar",
    "answer": "spielen"
  },
  {
    "question": "celebrar",
    "answer": "feiern"
  },
  {
    "question": "comprar",
    "answer": "kaufen"
  },
  {
    "question": "cocinar",
    "answer": "kochen"
  },
  {
    "question": "beber",
    "answer": "trinken"
  },
  {
    "question": "Georgia",
    "answer": "Georgien"
  },
  {
    "question": "los hermanos",
    "answer": "die Geschwister"
  },
  {
    "question": "los padres",
    "answer": "die Eltern"
  },
  {
    "question": "Turquía",
    "answer": "die Türkei"
  },
  {
    "question": "el estudiante",
    "answer": "der Student"
  },
  {
    "question": "el perro",
    "answer": "der Hund"
  },
  {
    "question": "el pastor alemán",
    "answer": "der Schäferhund"
  },
  {
    "question": "el fin de semana",
    "answer": "am Wochenende"
  },
  {
    "question": "en verano",
    "answer": "im Sommer"
  },
  {
    "question": "el cumpleaños",
    "answer": "der Geburtstag"
  },
  {
    "question": "la fruta",
    "answer": "das Obst"
  },
  {
    "question": "las verduras",
    "answer": "das Gemüse"
  },
  {
    "question": "la comida",
    "answer": "das Essen"
  },
  {
    "question": "el domingo",
    "answer": "am Sonntag"
  },
  {
    "question": "el agua",
    "answer": "das Wasser"
  },
  {
    "question": "la taza",
    "answer": "die Tasse"
  },
  {
    "question": "el té",
    "answer": "der Tee"
  },
  {
    "question": "viejo/a",
    "answer": "alt"
  },
  {
    "question": "soltero/a",
    "answer": "ledig"
  },
  {
    "question": "mucho/a",
    "answer": "viel"
  },
  {
    "question": "grande",
    "answer": "groß"
  },
  {
    "question": "negro y rubio/a",
    "answer": "schwarz-blond"
  },
  {
    "question": "fuerte",
    "answer": "stark"
  }
]